<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Zack Hubert</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Zack Hubert</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Incremental Work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-power-of-incremental-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-power-of-incremental-work/</guid>
      <description>Quite a while ago, I wrote a review of The New Turing Omnibus. A very clever book whose double entendre title reinforced the wit with which the subject matter was to be handled. In short, a very fun book that covers a lot of Computer Science topics.&#xA;What’s interesting though is how one tiny passage in the foreword changed my outlook on something important. Here it is:&#xA;Sometime during my childhood I encountered the traditional image of a bird that erodes a mountain by taking a single stone from it every year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Amazon Story</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/an-amazon-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/an-amazon-story/</guid>
      <description>This last week I was sitting with friends around a campfire and told the following true story. They found it rather interesting, so I figured it was worth retelling. The truth is, my career has been a really weird one…there’s nothing linear about any of the progression through work that I’ve chosen. It has been a truly wild ride, but I’m getting ahead of myself.&#xA;Amazon. 1999. It was a totally different company than it is now, though in many ways it’s probably still Day 1.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
